{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302282711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302282711"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 822dc89f-6bcc-4b74-ae71-1c28eca1a755"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-16-13"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302290172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302290172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 822dc89f-6bcc-4b74-ae71-1c28eca1a755"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-6-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302296507","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302296507"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 822dc89f-6bcc-4b74-ae71-1c28eca1a755"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-14"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302302860","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302302860"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 822dc89f-6bcc-4b74-ae71-1c28eca1a755"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302316610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302316610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 822dc89f-6bcc-4b74-ae71-1c28eca1a755"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_13-6-14"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302330312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302330312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 822dc89f-6bcc-4b74-ae71-1c28eca1a755"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-6-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302339155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302339154"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 822dc89f-6bcc-4b74-ae71-1c28eca1a755"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-6-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302345468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302345468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 822dc89f-6bcc-4b74-ae71-1c28eca1a755"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-6-14"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302352979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302352979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 822dc89f-6bcc-4b74-ae71-1c28eca1a755"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-13-7"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302360046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302360046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 822dc89f-6bcc-4b74-ae71-1c28eca1a755"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_16-3-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302365479","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302365479"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 822dc89f-6bcc-4b74-ae71-1c28eca1a755"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302398086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302398086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 822dc89f-6bcc-4b74-ae71-1c28eca1a755"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302403972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302403972"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 822dc89f-6bcc-4b74-ae71-1c28eca1a755"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302410613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302410612"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 822dc89f-6bcc-4b74-ae71-1c28eca1a755"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302416944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302416944"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 822dc89f-6bcc-4b74-ae71-1c28eca1a755"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302428177","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302428177"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302430822","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302430822"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302432375","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302432375"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302435324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302435324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302436883","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302436883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302439748","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302439748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302441302","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302441302"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302443970","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302443970"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302445527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302445527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302448488","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302448488"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302450037","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302450037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302453028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302453027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302454577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302454577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302457319","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302457319"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302458869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302458869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302461743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302461743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302463292","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302463291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302466694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302466694"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302468248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302468247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302471265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302471265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302472825","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302472825"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302476186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302476186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302477745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302477745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302480972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302480972"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302482529","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302482529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302485660","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302485660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302487227","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302487227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302490797","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302490796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302492381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302492381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302507501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302507501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302507587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302507587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302547796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302547795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" 5602b875-4254-46fe-b0b6-8face428d7d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302558868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302558867"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" e2c3fae1-47a6-4eb9-adff-76171547305a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302561847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302561847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" e2c3fae1-47a6-4eb9-adff-76171547305a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302565433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302565433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" e2c3fae1-47a6-4eb9-adff-76171547305a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302569007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302569007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" e2c3fae1-47a6-4eb9-adff-76171547305a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302576957","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302576957"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" e2c3fae1-47a6-4eb9-adff-76171547305a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302588190","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302588190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" e2c3fae1-47a6-4eb9-adff-76171547305a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548302602138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548302602137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_065746"," gameId":" e2c3fae1-47a6-4eb9-adff-76171547305a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}